''lt's a new age
A brand new world''
''This world keeps changing
generation to generation''
''lt's a new age
A brand new world''
''This world keeps changing
generation to generation''
''ln this world,
while you are busy with your life,
and while you look back to your past''
please don't forget to laugh''
''ln this world''
''when you learn to forget and,
when you learn to forgive''
''Don't forget to laugh''
ln 1984 - George was born
to David and Treesa.
Year 1999 - George passed
SSLC with first class.
Now - Year 2000..
l'm seriously in love with Mary.
Otherwise, no need!
l'm seeing Mary for the
first time at church.
When you read the bible that day...
the Churidhar you wore..
looked so gorgeous, you know!
Otherwise, no need!
What l said was...
Red-like Orange...
No..ORANCHA...no, it's wrong..
l'll write a new one.
Couldn't she have worn a blue churidhar?
10th AUGUST 2000 -ALUVA.
To my beloved Mary,
l'm seeing Mary for the
first time at church.
Mary, at church,
on the day of bible reading...
the Churidhar you wore, was so lovely!
Mary, you looked so...Ergh!!
Fishlady: Mackerel, Sardine,Tilapia
and Crab are available.
Mother: Son, which one do you want?
Mother: Which fish do you want?
Don't you know l like Sardine?
Why ask again and again?
Mother: That would stink up
the whole house.
Doesn't matter. Buy thin ones.
Mother: Shall l buy oily-sardine, then?
Will have full of bones, mummy!
Fishlady: Oh Come on!
lt doesn't have much of bones.
Mother: Get me one kg.
Mother: Betterto fry...
That'll be fine.
Then, l want 4 pieces...
Very crispy ones!
Mother: What about Anju then?
No need for her!
No problem if she doesn't eat sardine!
Unnichetan(shopowner): Hey Vinod,
Serve two cups of tea to Shambu and Koya.
Dude, l'm going to Bangalore
for my studies.
Jawad says, it's really a superb place!
Jawad? Who's that?
My Uncle's son.
Which Uncle's son?
Banana(''Kaaya'')merchant
in the market.
Banana! Was he the one, who named
you as Koya after ''Kaaya(Banana'')?
Yes, he only...
Brother, 7 banana fries
and one cup of tea.
How much tea? 7 huh?
Dude! Here comes Mary!
Where?
Brother, One parle G, please.
What else do you need?
And, one milk packet.
Seems like she'll buy stuffs
for home and leave soon.
Go and check if he's coming..
l've a doubt..
Does he love her or us?
Unpunctual christian!
Hey, is he coming?
Don't show off and lose
yourteeth needlessly.
Koya: Brother, one minute.
-Kuttapi: Ok, just a minute.
-Koya: Actually, l too said the same.
Kuttapi: That's what l said too.
Keeping eatables to tempt people!
Jahangir: Ah!..Oh my God!
Brother, one cigarette!
Take it.
Vinod, what are you trying to do?
lf at all you break the glass then..
-Mary: How much, brother?
-Shop owner: Rs.13.
Jahangir: Then, take this!!
Maju: My nose would have burnt now.
Shambu: She'll go now.
-Maju: You pervert! l'll rip you apart!
-Jahangir: Get lost, you build flirt!!
Maju: l know, where you're
going with this weightless bag.
Jahangir: You fool,
intelligent boys don't need books!
Maju: So, this bag is full
of your intelligence?
Shambu: l wonder where he has gone?
Mary: Ok brother
Hey sweety!
Sister, here's a black Hrithik Roshan!
Exactly!
Enough!
Sweety, went to study at school huh!
-Small girl: Get lost Monkey!!
- Mary: You come here
Sweet child, right!!
-Kolakozhi:Hey, Kuttapi!
- Kuttapi: What?
-Kolakozhi:Come out.
- Kuttapi:One minute.
Brother, flirts are growing a
lot around the shop.
Yes, one day, l will throw everyone out!
Then, l'll be left alone.
lncluding you also.
What's happening here?
Kolakozhi: Come on fast
Kuttapi: One banana, bro!
Kuttapi: ln the credit account of
Kolakozhi (water-hen).
Unnichetan(shopowner): Whose?
Kuttapi: Kolakozhi... Kolakozhi!
You will roll down somewhere.
Go slowly, man.
Hey Maju, are you not going?
l don't want to get a
punch from a kid.
-Kolakozhii: Come on, sit behind
- Kuttapi: Not possible, man!
Shiya: Better get down and
push the cycle, man.
Today, bull dog will definitely
rip off the feathers of Kolakozhi.
- Koya: Where the hell were you, man?
-George: Has she left?
Yes, she left
Oh my God! l was writing a letter.
Koya: Shaved off your moustache, huh?
George: Hmm! How do l look?
Awesome!
Shejust left.
Come, let's move that way.
Get the cycle.
Go fast, go fast
Celine, walk slowly.
Mary, shall l come to your house
to help you with homework?
My dad will be at home only tomorrow.
So, you come tomorrow.
lf your dad is not there,
then, l can teach you well.
No, not necessary.
Hey, white shirt!
Give me a little way, please.
-Move away, man!
- Get lost!
Mary...
lf you bump on Mary,
then,l'll bang you.
Don't mind them, Mary!
They are just stupids!
Brake it. Push....Push it hard...
''Haven't you heard, burnt stick should
be thrown out(malayalam proverb)''
How is it related to this situation!
Nothing in particular, you just push!!
Kolakozhi: Don't go.
l will buy ice-cream for you.
Be decent....decent..
Look, sister...
the guy we'd seen in the Church
Mary, don't look back.
Ugh! She looked?
-Just walk without noticing them
-Shambu: Dude, this is a positive sign.
Positive!
''On the bank of Aluva river,
when there was no one,
Slipping slowly,
December breeze came searching''
''Under the flowering tree,
when fragrance of flowers was wafting''
''slipping slowly,
naught breeze came searching''
''When l was in the Church,
you entered my heart without telling,
and started blowing whistles many times''
''When l was in the Church,
you entered my heart without telling,
and started blowing whistles many times''
''You are the first flower
which blossomed inside me''
''lf you give consent,
won't l tie the knot and take you away''
Church priest: George!!What's all this?
''There are no words to express
God's love''
''This life time is not enough
to express our gratitude''
''O love that protects
in times of difficulty''
''On the bank of Aluva river,
when there was no one,
Slipping slowly,
December breeze came searching''
''Under the flowering tree,
when fragrance of flowers was wafting''
''Slipping slowly,
naughty breeze came searching''
Flower?. Where?
When l was in the Church,
you entered my heart without telling,
and started blowing whistles many times''.
''When l was in the Church,
you entered my heart without telling,
and started blowing whistles many times''
''You are the first flower
which blossomed inside me''
''lf you give consent won't l tie
the knot and take you away''
''On the bank of Aluva river,
when there was no one,
''Slipping slowly,
December breeze came searching''
Get lost!!
Just after this turn, it's her house!
Go and give her the letter boldly!
This isjust a simple matter!
What's that sound?
Sounds like someone is coming running!
Why is he running?
Any dog chasing him?
Dog chased our Kolakozhi!
Get away...her dad....
Dad!!
Run and save yourself!
Dude, he fell!! Kolakozhi fell!
Bro, Move...move...l say move...
get on the cycle faster
Heck with your letter!
Kolakozhi: l swear, it was him.
Oh God, he caught our Kolakozhi!
Pedal it fast, man
-George: Cling onto me tightly, Koya
- Koya: l will never leave even if l die.
Shambu must have reached the
next district!
Koya: Your damn letter and Love!
Koya: Looks like Kolakozhi
has fallen into water.
Koya: Bro, pedal fast,
or else we'll also fall into the water.
George: Move away, fatso..move!
Kuttapi! l think your friend
is pushed into the water.
Kuttapi: Kolakozhi!
l think he's dead!
Koya: Shit! ls it a Puncture?
Hello!
Koya there?
Mom, keep down the receiver.
Who's this?
lt's me, George!
Oh you! Tell me!
l'm going to call her home now!
What is your opinion?
Bro, have you so soon forgotten,
Shambu slipped from the bicycle,
And, that fellow was chasing and hitting him,
didn't you see?
Hmm! Why don't you encourage me
like earlier?
lt's not because, l don't love you.
l'm scared! l am really scared of him!
Let me tell you another matter!
What's it?
What bullshit have you
written in that letter?
Mary looks like Sardine fry!
What look is that!!
Have l written like that?
Yes! You've written it like that!
Oh my God! Afisher woman had been
to my house at that time. Damn!!
Shucks! lt's because of that!
Then, write, ,AoFisher woman's' looks!
There are some more...
She's your Vaariyellu (Backbone)!
By the by, what's this Greek mythology?
This question is what l expect from her!
When l give her this letter,
she'll ask me what Greek Mythology is!
And l can explain to her
what Greek Mythology is, right?
lf you get caught in his hand...
he will tear your mythology apart!
Hey dude! What?
Go ahead!
What if l write a letter
to her in English?
ls it really needed?
No..No..Not needed, right?
And about calling her,
you ask Shambu also!
Okay, bye, good night!
Shambu!
-George: Hello
- Shambu's father: Hello!
ls Shambu there?
-Who's this? - Uncle, l'm George!
Oh George! Just a minute.
Shambu, call for you!
George is on the line!
Yes, coming.
What a time to call!
-Yes, tell me! - lt's me George!
Bro, l just now called up Koya,
about calling mary ...
he asked me to get your opinion also!
What a lovely idea!
Eh!! Shall l call herthen?
Yes!
-What's the noise there, shambu?
- Nothing! Nothing!
-Both of you better keep quiet!
- Lab result!
What's wrong with you?
Hey, move away...otherwise l'll..
Hey, you...Get away..
Everything will be fine as discussed!
Will see you tomorrow, okay!
What do you want? Huh? Get lost
Hey, Shambu...you....!
Dad, brother has got some bad book!
-Dad, lt's a film magazine.
-Yeah, l know!
Good lord!! Wouldn't she
have caller lD at home?
What happened to your face?
Mosquito bite!
lf mosquito, bites,
will it swell so big?
When mosquito bit, l beat it
and face got swollen.
Hmm....Mosquito!!
Unnichettan, flirts are at a rise now.
God, Will she pick my call today at least?
She might pick, right?
Someone will surely pick!
Last night, when l was
about to read that magazine...
my annoying brother saw and
was trying to get me caught,
dad asked and he was cool about it!
-Mary's father: Hello!
- George: Hello
Mary's father: who's it?
-ls Mary there?
-Yes, who's this speaking?
l'm George.
George!! Which George?
George, l have a Caller lD at home.
Who are you?
God! l'm a tuition mate, George Davidson.
Davidson?
Not Davidson!
l'm David's son of Kalaparambathul!
David Kalaparambathu!
-David Kalaparambathu? Oh!!
You were abroad, right? - Yes, yes!
How are you?
Any doubts?
Which subject?
Doubt in..
....in Chemistry! Doubt in Chemistry!
What's the doubt? Let me hear.
ls it Organic Chemistry?
-Dude, he is asking about the doubt?
-Say physics!
No..Not Chemistry..but Physics!
Mary..There's a call for you.
Ah Mary...!
That's great
Hello, Mary!
Yes, who's this?
l'm George!
George? Which George?
Ah, George! Mary,
When you leave, after class,
don't you see three guys after you?
Among them, l'm the mos
handsome guy George!
Shut up and Don't tell her
we ogled at her!
Cover the receiver!
Or, tell her l'm also glamorous.
Hello! Shall l meet you
over Aqueduct bridge tomorrow?
No..Not necessary.
What happened?
Not necessary, it seems.
Eh!! - NOT NECESSARY
That means...
the same - maybe not necessary!
Maybe she meant,
not to come and see her.
That's what l also said, right?
Anyway, l am not coming tomorrow.
You go!
-Dude! An idea!! - What?
Her dad's name is George,
and my name is also George.
Can't l say there's no need
for herto change her surname?
Fantastic idea!
-Koya: But you must tell this to her.
-George: l'll tell
-Why do l've to fear?
- ay boldly!
l'll say!
Say it quickly before her dad arrives.
Shambu, Have an eye at the front
and l'll take care of the backside.
Who's this in yellow shirt?
Sis! ls he taking part
in a Fancy dress show?
-That big house in Ras al-Khaimah..
- Okay!
Who the hell is he?
Papa - who prefers business as the
most important thing in life.
And Mom - is always
busy with night party and dance.
My only friends..
were the Arab friends
in Sharjah boarding school.
-Don't you have any sisters?
- No.
That Prince was living alone
in that big house.
Which Prince, bro?
You shut up, boy!
What is he saying? Arabic, huh?
Bro, please give way.
See, a Sachin Tendulkar behind you!
Hey, you ogler?.
ls that you - Girirajan Kozhi(Flirt)
Jojo!
ls this your usual business?
From where did you spring up, you demon?
l'm going to play Cricket. Give way.
Then, carry on with your Cricket. Go!
Go...and hit six!
Hey George... l've a tournament
at St.Mary's. Let me go.
Hey, bat.
Where did l stop?
When l was playing
football in Sharjah Cricket stadium,
my Arab friends asked me..
and my childhood was taken aback!
Yes, certainly!
Without love, sadly, l stood waiting..
And, thus started running for it.
Run...run..
At last, l found you!
Jancy...
Jancy? Oh sorry!
l love you.
Koya, come quickly..
Dude, tell me,
when you're about to run!
Who are you?
Who are you, man?
Exactly what l meant, who are you?
Who are these vagabonds
coming this way?
Who are you?
Why did you take off my glasses?
Why you removed?
Who are you?
Who are you, man?
l....l'm going to play cricket.
Who are you to ask me all this?
Did you only get my daughter
to play cricket with?
Aah (weeping), he hit me....
l understood one thing today.
Never ever trust you guys!
Why?
When that bull dog arrived,
you guys left me there and fled.
Do l've to say all this?
Don't you've sense to run?
Hey, l didn't notice him.
You must notice!
What a misfortune!
When l'd been there
with the letter forthe 1st time,
that Kolakozhi guy was there.
And today, who was that
yellow shirt Arabic guy?
Who the hell is he?
Fortunately, he was there!
Otherwise, we would've been
in deep trouble.
We would've been beaten up black
and blue if he wasn't there.
Oh!! Never!
l don't understand one thing though.
Why is it that all the
guys are after her?
Don't say that.
Hey, she's beautiful!
Really. Come on,
her hair resembles like a beehive!
She is beautiful?!
Dude! An idea!
Why don't we coax the
newspaper boy of her house?
And in between the newspaper..
let's keep a card, letter and a rose flower..
Keep a flower pot too..
What if it falls into the
hands of that bull dog(Mary's father)?
l see!!
Oh God!! Nothing is happening!
George, you please talk softly.
Everyone is here except mom.
Don't simply object every idea ...
Suggest some good idea.
To whom else can he say all this?
He has only us, right?
So, think well!
Give me a puff.
Koya: l'm thinking!
Yes, l got an idea!
Stop!
-Coming...Coming.
- Run...Run..
Who kept these benches here?
What are you guys up to?
You guys are going to
smash the shop!
lt was you, who let them in!
So, you throw all of them out.
That's enough!
Go and prepare tea!
Bye....Bye..
That ogler got enough!
Mary, your dad punched my eye red!
Mary, l want to tell you something.
About what?
No, l'll tell it to Mary.
Mary, why don't you ask him
what it's about?
l'll help you.
No thanks. Mary is in 12th grade now,
she can help herself!
l would like to tell you..
Mary, the cycle tyre
seems to have low air..
Don't worry.
We'll fill it on the way
Mary...
.. l would like to tell you something.
Hmm..come on.
Mary, let's go home.
We need to do our homework.
Give way. Let her take her cycle.
The road is too steep,
l'll help you out.
Sorry da!
l can help you if you need.
You take your cycle.
''l go to see her regularly''
''l see her without missing a day''
He asked me to talk to her
in front of him!
Who the hell does he think he is!
l'll push him down from the bridge.
''l can't hold without telling,
there's fire in my heart''
''l go to see her regularly''
''l see her without missing a day''
''lt is a pain which l hid in
my heart for many days''
''l can't hold without telling,
there's fire in my heart''
You said,
her dad is not at home..
-When did l say?
- Run..!
Who closed the gate?
Not me..Must be Shambu!
Before her dad sees us,
take the cycle and run.
''The eyes with moving waves
are Oleander flowers''
''They are like blossomed
cupid flowers''
''She is like gold melted
in sweet seventeen''
''She is a girl like a
rainbow which is painted''
''The eyes with moving waves
are Oleander flowers''
WHAT?
''They are like blossomed
cupid flowers''
Get lost, you Ogler!
''She is like gold melted
in sweet seventeen''
''She is a girl like a
rainbow which is painted''
A cracker burst overthere!
''l go to see her regularly
''l see her without missing a day''
''lt is a pain which l hid
in my heart for many days''
''l can't be without telling,
there's fire in my heart''
''Most of the ways and
tactics are wasted''
''l attend holy mass without a miss''
''l weep without getting sympathy''
''l follow her with no other way out''
''Most of the ways and
tactics are wasted''
''l attend holy mass without a miss''
''l weep without getting sympathy''
''What to say except
that this is Kaliyuga''
Stop there!
-Hey Maju
-What?
You keep playing!
lf you'd gotten married in your youth,
you could've played along with
your children now!
Getting married in 8th class?
Were you married at 8th class?
Bro, three glasses of Sarbath, please.
With soda or plain water?
Plain water!
Nothing seems to work out.
There's only one option left.
Go to the Church!
Church!? Don't l've any other work!
l hardly go forthe masses!!
Not the holy mass!
Won't Mary regularly go to the Church?
Propose at Church itself.
You saw her there for the
first time, isn't it?
Wonderful idea!
-ls'nt there no kas kas?
- There's!
What is kas kas for?
Kaskas will make you cool!
Church and all that are
fantastic ideas,
but when you go, don't go YOURSELF!!
Not as ME?
Take it, Shambu.
l mean...
-l too want kas kas.
,AiYou also?
Well, l won't be going by myself,
we'll be going together, right?
Go like an innocent studying boy!
Only then it'll work out.
Vinodh, Kaskas is almost over.
What if l write an
English letter and go?
No, is it?
l too want Kaskas.
You too?
No need of Church!
Her dad and mom will be around.
No....no Church...Drop it ..
l don't want to get beaten up.
Dude! l've a superb idea!
lf i go to the
bridge... her dad is there!
lf l go to the Church...
her dad is there!
Try giving her a call...
Wherever l go...
her dad is there everywhere.
Dude! An idea!
Why don't we cultivate this at home?
And why can't we take 1 kg
of coca to her house?
ls Coco-cola made from this?
No way! Or, is it true?
Coca-cola is made from this?
May be from itsjuice!
Dude! Look here.
Will this be fine?
l have seen that! l will smack you!
Rewind it , please!
l've not seen that!
Watch this now.
Good lord! The Bell over here is ringing.
When l managed to get a cassette finally...
Hell with his ideas!
l couldn't even watch it fully.
You said your dad will not be coming.
Shall l propose her on bended knee
and say l LOVE YOU?
No..no...you may hurt your hands and legs.
Yes, yes.
Shall l suggest another idea?
What if l deliver a dialogue from
the movie Thoovanathumbikal ?
Okay, carry on.
''We shall go to the village
and abode there''
''Over there...''
Oh, it's the dialogue from the movie called
'' Namukku Parkan Mundirithopukal''
Oh sorry! lt's ''Namukku
Parkan Mundirithopukal''
'' We shall go to the village
and abode there''
''Over there, grape vine
will be blossomed''
No....Not this..no need of all this.
Dude!! Tell......tell it in a simple way.
Shall l say it simple
straight and serious?
Mary, l love you.
And she will respond, ''George,
l don't love you''
ls this the serious tone?
No need of all this...
just tell it in a very simple way.
Shall l tell it in a simple way?
Mary, l love you.
Think it over and let me know.
l'm telling this from the deepest of my heart.
Enough...this will do.
Won't this be enough?
She's coming.
George?
Yes,
George!
He's also George!
Are you also George?
Yes!
-What do you do?
- Studying for Pre degree!
Oh...Pre degree! Holy Spirit!
Okay, l'm in SBOA!
Oh! You work in a Bank!
No....
No...School!
Oh!! School?! Ok!
Actually, l was waiting to meet you.
Yes!
You'd made a phone call to
my house that day, right?
l think Papa trusts you a lot!
And as there's Caller ld at home,
he will not be able to call
my home from Ernakulam!
Will any of you help him
to make a phone call from any of your places?
Oh no...People are always
around in my house.
l don't think it's possible.
lt's betterto opt for
some other option.
George?
lt's OK.. Doesn't matter.
Come again?
l've no problem!
You really mean it?
No, if it's trouble...
Not at all.
Thank you so much, George.
l always tell Mary..
that her dad's name is George,
and my name is also George
After marriage, there won't
be any need to change her surname!
Okay, see you then.
Shall l leave then... Bye,
Why did you agree?
Who asked you to agree?
You loser!!
Keep it safe !
Give it to her as you wish...move.
Coming?
Come if you want.
''Life is at bad phase''
''Physical appearance even worse''
''The luck-line grew faint
and disappeared''
''Life is at bad phase''
''Physical appearance even worse''
''The luck-line grew faint
and disappeared''
''The earth where l stood has sunk''
''All the good sights are fading away''
''The blossomed flowers
are withering away''
''Whatever l kept are also falling off''
''Life is at bad phase''
''Physical appearance even worse''
''The luck-line grew faint
and disappeared''
''Life is at bad phase''
''Physical appearance
even worse''
''The luck-line grew faint
and disappeared''
Yeah, l'll give him
''What all l had dreamed so far,
Got lost in reality''
''Whatever was in my heart,
Whatever was blooming
Someone or other took away''
''My beautiful expected future
got burnt away in front of my eyes''
''The ones l carefully preserved ,
were taken off from me before their time''
''The mango fruit which l kept tenderly
was plucked and taken away today''
-l am fed up-Don't weep like this
Brine mango!
Buddy...she..
Forget it...enough...go and cry..
lt's pretty hard, man!
Touchings are for that!
''All my sweet memories
which l had kept secretly
got perished and are buried O God!''
''Life is at bad phase''
''Physical appearance even worse''
''The luck-line grew faint
and disappeared''
''Life is at bad phase''
''Physical appearance even worse''
''The luck-line grew
faint and disappeared''
Hey, it's night!
Take off your glasses, you fool!
Hey Sibu!! Come, let's go home.
As if you won't find
any other girl on this land!
Hey, George! Dude!!
Get away before her dad comes
Good Lord! Why is he going there again?
When l passed 10th grade,
it was a great celebration at home.
Now, it looks like a mourning home!
ls failing in exams,
such a big problem?
Hmm...Now only l realized it.
Those fellows have passed in all exams,
except us..
Why do guys think we alone failed?
We should have studied something.
As we'd grown up like buffalos,
nobody lashed us at home.
What a shame!
Hereafter we have to reform ourselves!
What a pity!
Continuing in this way is not good.
Prayer call! l'm going to the mosque!
Give way.
l'm also leaving.
l've to reach home early.
2005-The year when
''Rajamanikyam'' movie was released
''Eyes are getting red''
''Teeth are biting in anger''
''Fists are ready for a punch''
''The whole body is sweating''
''Veins and arteries are pumping up''
''Muscles are stretching out''
''Heart is breathing fast,
in a rhythmic fashion''
Will it be a problem?
Problem?!
He promised to dance with us
and at the end left us when a girl called.
He deserves it!
lt's them!!
Oh Lord! He is coming
to kill me (screaming)
''Eyes are getting red''
''Teeth are biting in anger''
''Fists are ready for a punch''
''The whole body is sweating''
''Veins and arteries are pumping up''
''Muscles are stretching out''
''Heart is breathing fast
in a rhythmic fashion''
''Hands and legs are shivering''
''And craving for a fight''
''The whole body is getting aggressive''
''And shivering from
top to toe like an Oracle''
SUSPENDED FOR 2 MONTHS
BHARGAVlNlLAYAM (House Name)
Rummy!!
So, for this you shouted!
Big deal!
Well the Game is over!
Lost in this game also!
What do you want?
Give a smack on it , dude!!
-You do it!
- Do it, l say
Get off you!
Couldn't find any joker until this time?
Go and check the mirror.
Where's George?
Here he comes!
Looking handsome after bath!!
Hey, you stupid..don't break it.
Get up guys.....Lets go to College.
Newcomers are joining today.
We need to rag them, let's go
This game will get over soon.
Playing cards like children!
-Koya, are you also leaving? - Yes
Shambu, give the cigarette and go.
WELCOME NEWCOMERS
Sindu...Bindu....Wow!!
Here's Bolt Anoop!
lt was in the morning.
Did you see the symbol? Symbol?
Benz Symbol!!
Must be lying down somewhere there.
George, you saw my car's symbol?
Good Lord that you didn't lose your car!
Get lost you Bolt!
What is your name?
Giraffe?!!
Oh Jaffar!! Are you scared?
Put your hand down.
Come here.
-What's your name?
-Varsha
-Yours?
-Shilpa
-Which Course?
- B.com
-Eh?
,AiB.com
Why don't you dance then?
Dance??
Shambu! Sing a song.
'Malayalam song'
We belong to poor families.
Don't poor children dance?
We're also from poor families.
We've danced a lot.
Something else..
What else?
Where are you going?
Got sunglasses and all?
Why don't you take
a shower in the morning?
l had, bro!
-Won't you dance?
-Of course!
Good. Shambu, sing a song.
'Tamil song'.
See....this is how you should dance.
-What's your name?
- Moosa
Which Course?
B.Sc Computer science!
Oh!! Our department.
Good!
Bye, bro!
Hey Saree!! Come here..
What is this? Morning itself in saree!
What's your name?
- Malar!
Malar?
-l said my name.
-Yours?
Ah! Tamil?
Yes!! Fantastic!
l'm George David.
Which course are you studying here?
l'm not a student.
l'm here to teach.
l'm a guest lecturer.
Ehh!! Next Suspension on the row!!
Which course are you studying here?
We're also thinking the same.
B.Sc...Final.
B.SC Computer science.
Your name?
Koya!!
Don't complain to teachers!!
l'll not..
Shambu
Oh nice!
Can we go, teacher?.
Please escape us from these dirty people..
they're ragging us..
What a pathetic english is this!!
All that is between you people!
But when you wander alone at night,
or while you're on the road alone,
you need to be brave, right?
And for that, such ragging and all
is ok....alright?
Okay, l'll leave now.
See you in class.
Go...go... go to your classes.
Shucks!! She is a teacher!!
Give me the stuff!
-What is this?
- Spirit!
lt's superb!
lf you want to see Usman,
come outside the college!!
Then, come outside the college!!
Dude
What's this George?
Don't you know it's not Sharbat?
Hello all!
Good morning, Miss!
Sit down...Sit down, please.
So, l'm Malar.
l will be teaching System Analysis
and Design in this Semester
And l'm from
Kodaikanal basically so..
Now l think you should
introduce yourselves.
Start from here.
Look, he's standing up.
Make him sit! George!
-l'm Aswathi from Aluva...
-Nice...you?
Ma'am, l'm Deepa from Thrissur.
You?
l'm Anjali from Aluva.
Ah ah! You?
What's that? Stand up!
-Caught!!
- What's that in your hand?
Tell it's a Cough syrup!
Pepsi!
Ma'am...my friends gave this.
Can't you tell it's not you??
Was it you?
Tell her it's not us.
Three of you...Stand up.
She is asking whether it is you?
Yes, miss!
Alcohol is fine , okay.
But l'm not going to permit
this in my class.
Good decision!
All right!
All four of you, please leave
the class right now.
Leave now.
-Ma'am, do l also have to leave?
-Yes, all of you.
Oh ok, thank you!
Not only suspension..
Perhaps a TC also!
Teacher, one minute.
Dude! Dude!
What?
You know..
Don't think l'm saying because..
l'm drunk.
Hey, George.....
-What's this?
-Just a minute.
You look so very beautiful!
Totally finished!
Koya, Shambu... Come here.
-Take him away.-l know..
-Take him.
- Yes, will take him
So, students, where did we stop?
Sir, l've something to tell you.
Sir your taking a lot of time,
Come fast.
You please think...
How am l to tell this to my mother...
You tell her, sir...
Why are you afraid?
Tell her boldly.
See students are coming..
Throw off the cigarette.
Oh, little more was left.
Mr.Lonappan
Reached, huh?
What do you like to have?
3 Cups of tea and 3 Banana roast.
No need....3 lime and 3 Banana roast.
Sir, how will l tell my mother
that my lover is a tamil girl?
What a beautiful name?!!
what?
Malar!
What's your intention?
Remember, she's a teacher.
But l loved her at
first sight itself!
Huh!!!
But teacher has just joined college
and so soon you fell in love with her?
For that you need to
propose teacherfirst, right?
Sir, to fall in love it
just takes one second.
l loved her at the first sight itself.
Did l know that she is a teacher?
What if she is a collector or a teacher?.
l don't care!
Then, job?
After this course, l'll look out
for a job in the Sutherlands.
l'll be paid a handsome pay.
then, my family...
My dad is an open minded person.
He'll understand.
-And mom, she may also agree.
-They might agree too.
What are you going to tell her, sir?.
Tell me, let me also hear.
Come on, let me hear
Do l've to say it out here?
Yes, sir.
-Sir, are you going to say?
- Yes!
Then say!
l love you.
Get lost man!
lf at all, there's any problem,
after seeing a little baby,
everything will be fine.
-Really pathetic, sir!! ,Ails it?
Dude, this morning
we saw the teacher..
We went to her class
and she threw us out.
- ln such a short time...
-How are you...?
To whom am l saying this!
Dude, this morning we saw the teacher..
We went to her class
and she threw us out.
ln such a short time,
you thought of all this??
Let's not use the word TEACHER
l feel lot of distance with her!!
Why can't we call her informally?
-HER!!SHE!!...
-Wait
Won't this SHE be older than him?
Dude, Sachin married a
woman elder to him, right?
But the only difference is,
that is SACHlN and here, it is HlM.
That's what l also said.
Then.... she has pimples.
What's wrong with that?
All of us have had pimples, right!
Pimples is not at all problem, dude!
That's not an issue, but surely the
other thing would be a problem .
Other thing? What?
-Different country....
-Country?
No...District..
l mean different State
So what? All of us are lndians!!
- l want to buy some Tamil CDs
- What for?
So, that l can learn some Tamil!
(Malayalam film dialogue)
You'll mess up everything.
Dude, say sorry!!
Me? Never!!
We'll be in trouble for internal exam then.
Mind you!!
Jerry sir and all are like that.
What if miss is also the same
Bro, we have to say sorry before
madam complains about us.
Even otherwise, just imagine,
if the Principal learns about this..
Remember, you already
have two suspensions.
You guys also have suspensions, right?
But you have more than us.
She will have a good impression
only if you say sorry.
Otherwise just think about it. We will be
considered as drunken mischief students.
Who is he? Bheeman Raghu (Actor)
ln Spadikam (Malayalam film )
l'll do one thing.
l'll get her number and
call her tonight.
lmpossible! All that won't work out.
-Don't even think of getting her number!
- Why is that?
lmpossible
Sir, you come..
Come!
Er....Sir...come.
Sir, You come here
Sir, it's not necessary now..
Sir you need to do it now
Sir, you can do it! Come on, sir.
-Hi! - Hi
-Hello!-Hello
Come on say!
Can you give me your mobile number, please?
Ahh!! 98941 ..
One second please.
What the hell is happening here?
Say! Say!
Thanks! Study well, okay!
Uh..how come you guys in class?
-Why are we here for?.
-No, we've a doubt!!
Sir...got it..
Actually, last number was 6...
l gave it wrong.
And you guys?
You guys wanted to tell me
something, right?
Ah....that's...actually..
We're sorry.
-Sorry...-Sorry.
Please don't complain to the Principal.
Let me think it over and say.
l'll think about it.
Let's go....
Let's go...
Super she is!!
You come here.
Not enough, right??
Simple!
Java is very simple.
And also Powerful.
Very powerful.
Then safe too!
Java is very safe.
Are you able to understand anything?
Anjali, are you able to
follow what l'm saying?
lf not, better ask me, got it?
l'm telling it to all of you..
lf your not able to follow,
do ask me.
-Then comes Robust!
-You mean Robusta banana!
lt's not the banana!
Robust means..
lt's explained on the page.
Refer your text book after some time.
- Sir
Get in..Get in please
Has this fellow started
his class early today?!!
l was teaching Java.
Java is very easy to learn.
So, you will be able to
follow it very easily.
What we were talking about was
properties of Java,
lt's simple and powerful.
Did you understand?
lt's also safe
Got scared?!
Shucks!
What are you doing?
l didn't see you yesterday.
l was there.
Really! l didn't see you!
l saw.
MAVA...
Sir, lt's not MAVA but JAVA
Sorry..sorry...JAVA
The next topic is lnheri...
lnheritance!
Take 25th page in your textbook
No textbook.
ln that, you can see a cat
peeping out from the window,
and the dog eating meat outside!
Look
Were you able to understand?
l've also not understood it correctly.
Let's jump to the next topic.
Overriding! What's overriding?
Tell me.
l think he knows nothing
about this subject!
What's meant by overriding?
Tell me.
Somebody answer!
George, Koya, Shambu and Suresh
Principal wants to meet you.
Sir, the Principal has called
you too to his cabin.
lf your son goes this way,
then the situation would get worse.
Regarding the explosion incident
l actually wanted to dismiss him.
And, then l changed it to 2 months
Suspension only based on your promise!
Last day, he missed his phone
in the Canteen.
Concerned people handed
overthe phone to me.
When l looked at his
phone's Wallpaper,
lt read ''GET LOST YOU DOG''
Doesn't your son have any culture?
A couple of days back,
for consuming alcohol in class,
Malar teacher threw him
out of the class.
But teacher didn't tell me!
Forthat, she'll be taken to task later!
ln fact, this was informed
to me by a student's mother!
She asked whether her daughter's
classmates were drunkards?
Honestly speaking,
l felt my skin peeling!
See, look at him. When l'm
discussing something seriously,
look at the way he giggles!
What nonsense is this!! Laughing?
Here on, lf l ever see you
laughing for any jokes..
Heard me..?
And regarding the blast incident....
lt hasn't been proved in
my son's name, right!!
So, just don't try
to pin up that blame on my son!
Passover that credit to somebody else.
And you were complaining about
some Dog or Cat...on his mobile..
Sir, Those are the words
in the dictionary.
These words are not
unparliamentary, right?
And consumption of alcohol..
l too don't like it.
Son, hereafter, don't enter class
after consuming alcohol.
And lf you want to,
drink at home or in a bar.
What sort of a dad are you?
Are you encouraging your son to drink?
We normally don't create
any nuisance publicly after drinking.
And l've said that to him too.
And if you ever call me complaining
about Dog...cat and all...
then, you'll see my true nature.
Aren't we sending our children here,
trusting them in the hands of
such extraordinary men??
Can't they reform our
children if they wished??
Don't you bloody try to trouble me
ever again for such petty flimsy issues!
Awesome!
Malar, please take care of Mr.George.
Ah! Let it be like that
George, come.
Does anyone set a Wallpaper as
''Get lost you Dog''
lt was not me,
that was Bolt who did it!
Oh, l see! l too thought
you've become so cheap!
And l really disliked the way
yourfoolish Principal complained about you.
-That's why l punched him with my words
-That's Good!!
And your last English dialogue...
You really killed it!
Come...Come..
She hasn't noticed...
Today, l'll listen in class properly.
Now, who can give me
the definition of a system?
Please stand up.
Who?
When did you three come into class?
Are you happy now?
You three in the last bench!
Shucks, this bench doesn't even
allow us to sit. Very unlucky bench
Please get out of the class.
Let's go and eat Banana roast!
3 lime and 3 banana roast!
One with extra sugar!
Ok Sure
O God!
What happened?
She threw us out of class
because we were late, right!
Ugh!!
Oh! Should have come
earlier if you wanted!
So, now you're on her side!!
Miss, l've a doubt.
Dude! What you doing?
Go inside and look!!
Stop messing around.
Class is going on.
-What the hell is he doing
- Shh! Shut up.
Whoo!
l'll howl if l want to! Be decent.
What's this like school children...!
Thrown out of the class!
Guys, your teacher is a superfigure!!
Mother , Father, Guru, and God, isn't
it that way!
Go..
Mother, Father, Guru and God!!
You hit him for that huh?
Oh!! Come on!! Don't giggle like a kid!!
Stop blushing.
See, this is what l hate!
So what! Let him look.
So you come to my class on time!
-Okay?-Okay
Now, you can go to class..
and you stay here.
Me?
Yeah, you!
You can go to the class.
Yeah, you can go to the classes!
Going in the wrong direction
Sir, Why is he...
Sir, don't worry. Come
You move
Malar miss! l messaged you yesterday.
l waited for so long.
No message came back.
So l called you back,
an old woman took the phone.
l just cut the phone. l got scared
Okay, that was my warden.
She read the message
and said you sounded like a flirt!
Flirt?!
Flirt means?
Rooster!!
Hi Malar! How is George?
He's good, sir.
But a little late for class.
l'll take care of him.
l didn't expect this from these people.
Great effort!!
l never expected that
you would reform them so much!
Thank you, sir.
Sir, did you really mean it
or were you mocking us?
What do you think?
-Felt like you mocked us-
Sir, l'm going to class!
A good improvement!
Carry on!
We're going, sir.
Thank you, sir!
George, this evening, at the ground....
Don't come...okay.
-Hi!! So, what's your name?
- Malar
-l'm Murali.
-Oh nice!
Which one?
See... See that dude!!
Can you see her?
''You walk around talking like a
Cute little girl, my beauty''
''What ecstasy her cheeks , eyelids
and smile are altogether giving me.''
''Why did a thousand
lightnings strike me''
''What this love is doing to me''
''Truth and lie seem the same''
''Like a new rhythm in my heart,''
''Shall l love you forever.''
''You walk around talking like a
Cute little girl, my beauty''
-Did she send this?
- l first messaged her.
And, then she replied back.
You naughty little!!
''Oh Love, it is me your lover
writing this affectionate letter''
lf l call Nigil,
will l be able to recharge?
''When l think of you, poems overflow''
''When l am going to write,
l can't find the words''
''Oh Love, it is me your lover
writing this affectionate letter''
What is this? Market?
Please sit down.
You didn't order anything?
We did.
No problem, you can order
anything you want
-Shall l order anything?
-Sure Please carry on!
Bro! Three Beef roast
and three rice cakes!
For me, one rice cake and banana.
Lonappan(canteen owner):
lsn't Shivan sir eating anything?
-Vimal Sir: Sir, you don't want anything?
-l need a banana.
One boiled banana for sir.
Boiled?
Two numbers.
My mother is looking for a
good alliance for me.
Oh! l see!! Really good!
But l found my dream girl!
Wow!! Fantastic!!
But l've not yet expressed
my wish to Miss.
-Miss?
Which Miss?
That new Tha...
That new Tamil teacher only!
Sir, won't there be
any issue in yourfamily?
For that, he has to first tell it to Teacher
and then worry about home, right?
Enough, right?
George, you must help me.
You'll talk high about me
to the teacher.
-Right, sir?
- Yes
Tell her this Vimal sir is good hearted..
-..and he has lots of money.
-Oh ok !
Sir, tell about sports...
Yes, Vimal sir is a good sprinter,
good jumper
-Good singer..
- Sir, that's not needed.
-No need to say that?
,AiNo, that'll be pathetic!
Then you guys can mention about my dance...
that l'm a good dancer.
l'll say about dance!
No, that l'll tell..
then, l'll tell about your running!
l think l missed out on something...
Banana hasn't come yet.
Ah!! Yes! You can also say Vimal sir
owns lot of land in Tamil Nadu.
Sir, then Kodaikanal is enough!
That's teacher's hometown.
-No...Not Kodaikanal!
-No?
Tiruchy, Salem... Ooty!!
Yes , lovely place!
A very cool place.
How many acres of land should l say?
-Say around 20 - 30 acres
- Ok
Raise it some more!!
The land value is quite less there.
-Oh is it so?
-Yes
Sir, then shall l say 50 acres?
Oh no, 50 acres are very less.
No impression. Say 900 acres!!
-900 acres?!
-Sir, you can surely say that figure!
Saying 900 acres is much better
-Really? -Why not! Anyways,
we're simply saying right?
By the way, ln 900 acres....
What should l say is being cultivated?
Rubber!
-Rubber in Ooty!!
-Yeah
Jackfruit!!
There's no Rubber in Ooty??
Get lost!
-Yes!! Carrot!!How about it!!
-Yeah Carrot!
No!! Cardamom!! That's enough.
Cardamom Estate in Ooty!!
Good!!
How about we say PEARS?
Yes!! Right!! Pears!!
-Very good!
-Awesome!!
900 acres! Pears Estate in Ooty!
We'll fix it, right?
-How about a pond too.
-Yes...good!
-Crocodile!
-Crocodile?!
No Crocodile!
MAAVA
So, sir owns 900 acres
of the Pears estate in Ooty!!
Who is that who called me?
Beef is not good enough.
Who called me?
Sir, let's go.
Are you not going to class?
We'll finish this and join sir.
By the way,
no problem if you don't attend!
lf any problem arises,
just mention my name.
A SMALL BREAK
He looks very smart and handsome!!
-Good ''Gym'' toned man!
- ''Gym'' man?
Looks like her would-be !!
Let me go. l've to see my girl.
Hi!! l've been looking for you.
He's my Cousin Arivazghan!
We call him Arivu!
Okay, he's Shambu...
This is Koya...my student.
-This is George
- Hi George!
My...Student only...
Oh , okay!
We are just going to have lunch.
You guys want to join?
Ah!! Nice Canteen is pretty close by.
ls Chicken Biriyani available there?
Eh?! You know Malayalam?
Little little!
-Come.
-Yeah, sure!
Saji, get everything ready fast.
lt was really a deceit!
Now, l must look out for Shilpa.
Would you share a half plate
of Chicken biriyani, if l order?
Who's this Shilpa?
Have l not told you?
Anything will happen over the phone!
Note down the number.
Sir, he might be her brother, right!!
Sir, can you order a plate of
Pearlspot fry...eh...l mean Seer fry
-Hello bro..
- Yes, what do you want?
One Seerfry!
Look at him!
Good body!
And pretty handsome too!
Sir, do you know what my problem is?
Superb pickle!
l've no hair!
Sir, it's good you don't have hair!
You look handsome this way.
lf you'd had hair,
then you wouldn't have looked good.
This really suits you!
Sir, l..
What? Want to fly?
Why don't l set up a wig
like the one film stars keep?
lf you keep a wig,
it will look like a lightening struck crow,
run over by a lorry and made dry...
kept on the head!
-No need of all that!
- lt will look really pathetic!
Sir, you first eat well and become healthy.
Anyhow, you can't match
up to his glamour and looks..
At least you can match up with your health.
Let us eat fish first and then decide.
Okay?
Enough?
Wow!!
Oh my God! Rice?!
Sir, will you say?
What to say?
Seerfish fry has been served
and rice is over.
Lonappan will tease me
if l ask for more rice.
Sir, you say!
-Lonappan-Yes, sir!
He needs some more rice.
Saji, serve some rice for Shivan sir!
-Fish fry! Do you want?
-l don't need anything
Do you need anything else?
Are you a Tamilian?
You know Liberty theatre in Kodambakkam,
Yes, l know..
l worked at a tea stall opposite to it.
That's what l was wondering
how you spoke Tamil so fluently.
l worked there for almost 3 yrs.
Oh, okay!!
Which place do you belong to?
l'm also from Kodaikanal,
next to Malar miss's house.
Oh! Malar miss's friend?
No! l'm her cousin.
Sir, he might be her lover, isn't it?
No, might be her brother?
See..their ears look alike.
Yes!
ln appearance too..right?
MAAVA...MAAVA...
lt's time for you to leave, sir!
Have no penny in hand....
have no penny in hand..
Arivazhagan!! What handsome looks he's got!
Really a charming guy!
Yeah!! Good physique and charming smile!
l still have a doubt.
Why do you always have
this never ending doubts?
You always have doubts on everything
l was talking about the game.
Hey, you got yourself fooled!!!
Give Rs.10....
- l don't have
He would've left (Arivazhagan)??
l don't think so?
Most probably he would stay here.
Dude, is it her?
May be she's calling
to invite you for dinner with them.
Anyways, we're not coming
and you too can't go, understand?
Don't go, okay?
Hi George!! What were you doing?
Uh..wejust had dinner.
ls it? What did you have?
Ah....
Dude, what did we eat?
Eh?
She's asking me what l had for dinner?
Tell parotta and beef!
Ah...hmm.. l had parotta and beef.
You didn't like me introducing
you as my student to Arivu, right?
Yes!!(Aama )
Tortoise ah!!(Aama in Malayalam is Tortoise)
Am l your student?
Yes! Of course you are my student, right?
Don't get angry, please.
He left that time itself.
l was washing my clothes,
hence l didn't pick up the call.
Sorry!
When you come tomorrow,
will you get me
Malli poovu(Jasmine Flowers)?
Malli Poovu?!
Malli podi...(Coriander powder)?
Jasmine Flower!
l always go to the temple keeping flowers.
Oh!! You mean Mulla poovu!! (Jasmine flower)!
Ah!! l'll get it for you !.
Okay, l'm going to wash my clothes now.
Okay, good night!
Yeah, good night!!
-Rummy! Who said?
-You only told.
You should have the same number
and same colour.
l asked in the beginning itself
Better stop this here.
Where will l get Jasmine flower?
Malli Poovu!!?
ls it Malli Podi (Coriander powder) ?
Oh, sorry! Where do l get Jasmine flowers?
You will have to go
early morning itself.
You will get it in the junction.
You'll have to go alone, okay?
None of us will accompany you.
Jasmine flower(Malli Poovu)!!
ls'nt it enough to go tomorrow morning!
-Shambu get up...come.
- What is the matter?
-Come with me
- l am not coming...Then,
One more thing..
When your going, don't go yourself.
So, you guys are not coming?
Not that, if three of us set out together,
then police will catch us.
l'm not coming.
This will only work
if you go as a studious-decent person
Dude, She threw him out for
consuming alcohol on the first day itself.
Then, how can he ever
look like a decent fellow?
This is George...My stu..
My friend.
This is Malar...sorry Nandini, My roommate.
George, where is your house?
My house is nearby.
You're a Mosquito?
My God! l'm getting a call.
Who's this troublesome....!
''When the sky is decorated
with colours of rainbow''
''A colourful dream is blossoming in me''
''Wind blowing through this river side''
''ls like the tunes from a
flute weaved with thrill''
''During the time when l
experienced this cool dream''
''A spring season came to my heart''
''The peacock couples sleeping
inside me wake up''
''And my inside is filling up with love''
''O beauty,
You are like a beautiful sculpture''
''O flower,
You are the rose flower
blossoming inside me''
''Flower, in your absence all the colours,
which decorated me are fading off'
''lf you are not showing mercy
to come beside me''
''All the beautiful dreams are
going away the beats and rhythms''
''Which l have kept deep inside
my soul tenderly''
''Without anyone's knowledge
are coming out as tunes ,
and colours''
''You are raining inside
my broken heart''
''As a romantic rain this beautiful day''
''Flower, my tiring body is waking up''
''Because of your lashing love''
''O beauty''
Nice shirt!
Not shirt! Kurta!
Kurta!!
Kerala Saree...Looking super!
''During the time when l
experienced this cool dream''
''A spring season came to my heart''
''The peacock couples
sleeping inside me wake up''
''And my inside is filling up with love''
''O beauty,
you are like a beautiful sculpture''
''O flower,
You are the rose flower
blossoming inside me''
We can try a simple step first
Please rewind!
Ready?
Ready!!
Once more, let me wear my shades
Rewind it again.
lf l don't wear my sunglasses
then my steps would go wrong
For each dance.... l need a different glass!
That,Aos D'cruz style!
Come on play!
Come on! Position..
Now turn
You must concentrate well and dance
This way..Do it!
9P.puz ow
One minute, phone is ringing
Hello Ancy!! What's up? Tell me..
Oh, dad is not at home?
Shucks!! Couldn't you tell me this earlier?.
l have come here to teach Dance.
ls this fellow teaching
dance steps over the phone?
Come on! Only three boys! No girls!
He has not even taught a single line!
Full time over the phone!!
Hell with him!
Shall l beat him to death ?
Do l avoid calling you........?
Hey! l got a new dance step! Awesome!
Maju! Come!
Yesterday only
l missed out on calling you,
still you
get upset. Don't get upset!
Just a minute.
l'll call you back
What are you guys doing
in the Kitchen? Cooking?
l'm Shiya.
l'm D'cruz!
l have another name too
Blacky?? !!
What's the problem here?
Where will we find a dance teacher?
-Dude! l know a dancer
-who?
Dolly!!
Super!!
Get off from here!
Hell with your Dolly!
ls he dumb ?
lt's full of ants inside.
Can't you close it and keep?
Hello! Are you very busy?
Ah!! Malayalam?
Yes ,yes!
Again, Malayalam?
Okay, what are you doing?
Now...searching for a dance master.
We got one guy!
But he's always over the phone.
Shall l do the Choreography?
Eh!! You know to dance?
To whom do you think
you are asking this question?
Maybe not upto the mark....
... l've won some State level prizes!
Oh! l see!!
What type of dance...
Kuchipudi, Bharatanatyam..?
No..Break dance!
l think l'll rewind
and see one more time.
Can you make the steps a
little more easier?
Sure!
Okay!!
See this, how simple it is !!
No...never.
Then l will show another one
Keep your hand this way....like this...
How she twists her legs?
Not leg, but hand...See this
Sir, you know what
l am trying to tell you
Don't you know any simple steps?
Like this
Sir, l don't know any simple steps.
Can't l impress her with such steps?
Perhaps possible!!
But l know only difficult steps
Please watch, sir.
lt's not simple...horrible!
See that... What is that??
Seeing her do that, those guys
themselves are running away.
Come, let's go sir...
-Paada!!(difficult), right?-Yes
Certainly! These are quite difficult!
lt's impossible for me to do.
l meant Paada (Sing a song)
Sir, l think that would be
much better an idea!
Sing a song or tell a
story what so ever...!
By just watching this,
we'd break our bones..
Singing itself is enough
He left! He's not coming anymore.
Who?
Moosa! He left!
Where did he go?
Who knows?
Didn't he come for the match?
No.
-Shucks ,AiShucks
l doubt Justin!
l think he's behind this.
Bloody hell!
What on earth shall we do now?
How are we going to find a substitute?
Hey....l've warned you several
times not to put my t-shirt and roam around.
Fusspot! l'll wash and give.
Oh com'on!! Have you ever washed it?
When have you washed it?
l...
Look at this... thread is coming off...
Take it off.
-l say remove it now
-Ok l'll give you.
You guys always fight for silly things!!
lt is my new T-shirt..
Not even once l've worn it.
Ergh! Don't sit and drink like that...
Give it to me.
Give some suggestion !!.
We're short of a person.
l'll give an idea...
Lets get a substitute from outside.
Don't talk foolishly!
Won't they find out?
Don't you know our Principal?
He will sniff and find out!
How can he find
one among 10 - 15 people?
He will take it as some college bunker !
Just like us!
What will Malar miss say?
What will Malar say?
l'll convince her.
You think Malar will not heed my words?
Good if she listens!
By the way whom are you intending?
l know a person in my church!
He knows to sing and dance quite well.
Why don't l call him?
-What's his name?
- Jojo!
Really a rocking song!
l feel like dancing.
Hello..this is'nt that strong..
No. lt's quite strong.
Shall l show you the steps?
No need. We've already
practiced the steps.
You just dance for us.
Who's the teacher? Dolly?
No...miss.
Miss?
Who's that?
Our teacher. Malar Miss.
What programme is this?
For college arts festival
O my God!! l won't dance for
the college folk dance.
After listening to this song...
do you feel it's a folk?
No.
Then, what?
That's why l said,
l don't perform folk dance.
Now, l'll dance..come..
Come on
-Will it work ?
-Probably run!
Come on warm up...
then only our body will be flexible...
Come...on....show the dance step
''Hey , lam going to sing a song''
''l cannot stay without dancing anymore''
''lt whistles all around the town''
''This is kuthu (tamil beat)
and rock dance, you hear''
''Hey , lam going to sing a song''
''l cannot stay without dancing anymore''
''lt whistles all around the town''
''This is kuthu (tamil beat)
and rock dance, you hear''
''Rock is the big thing there''
''Kuthu (tamil beat) is the big thing here''
''The combination of both is mass''
''Say, do re me fa so la ti do''
''lf rock and kuthu (tamil beat)
are combined,''
''lt's rockaan kuthu''
''lf rock and kuthu (tamil beat)
are combined,''
''lt's rockaan kuthu''
''The kuthu (tamil beat)
of western people ls rock''
''The rock of our area
is kuthu (tamil beat)''
''l grew up hearing Michael
Jackson songs''
''l grew up singing llayaraja songs''
''Just try the tea from nair tea shop''
''The soda
of western people ls coco-cola''
''A thousand watts bulb means
powerto light up''
''Look at the barking dog''
''God is above all of us''
''No need of competing''
''All music are the same''
''That is my opinion also''
''Say sa ri ga ma pa da ni sa''
''lf rock and kuthu (tamil beat)
are combined,''
''lt's rockaan kuthu''
''lf rock and kuthu (tamil beat)
are combined,''
''lt's rockaan kuthu''
''Hey, mass kuthu''
''Hey, weight kuthu''
''Do right kuthu''
''This is rockaan kuthu''
Give a big round of applause for that,
mind blowing performance from
George and team!!
Dude, you really rocked it!
-How was it?
-Dude, really rocked!
Splendid!
Marvellous!Dude
Keep it.
Don't forget...evening at Bhargavi! Okay?
-So how's our programme?
-lt was amazing!
No, l didn't mean that..
if you give my payment...
l'll go right away.
Payment?
Yes! l dance for money.
Rs.1000 - my payment!
1000?
Bro! We can only afford this much now.
Shut up.
You go now. l'll somehow give
you the money tomorrow.
l swear. You go.
Better!! Otherwise, l'll come to
the college tomorrow.Mind you.
Cover your face with the
dhoti in your hand!
lf you don't pay me tomorrow,
l'll pull off your dhotis in the college!
lt was super! Awesome!
Spellbound!!
You know, even l was tempted to whistle!
Oh, come on fast!
Where's my glass?
Carry him.
Call the ambulance!
Arivu is waiting. l'll leave.
Malar, miss you!
Bye!
-Bye...ME too....See you.
-Koya..Shambu...bye!
-Shall we go?
- Yes
Shall l ask you guys a doubt?
How do we fall in love?
Buddy...love....is a very special feeling!
...an intense feeling...
That's ...whenever we think of someone,
we feel very happy!
....like a pleasant music!
Have you heard illayaraja's songs?
''Oh my love! This is...
a letter your lover writes''
Where is your lover now?
Above!
Above? Above who?
Above my house...for rent.
Oh God!! That'll really land in a fix!
Take your lover away from there.
Move your lover to Kodaikanal...
...or Ooty!
Otherwise love somebody in Ooty!
Go on a journey with your lover.
While on the journey, some incidents would
happen... that'l give you the feeling..
My life gets stranded....!
l still don't understand the place to travel!
You'll not be able to understand.
That's LOVE
Next song will be sung by Shambu.
MESSAGE TO MALAR
You guys are able to follow, right?
Otherwise better ask me.
NOTlCE
Guest lecturer Malar has,
..discontinued herteaching career here.
She had met with an accident,
and has recovered safely.
She's staying with her parents.
Please pray for her fast recovery.
-George! -Hi! Hi!
Koya...Shambu...How are you?
-This is...-Ourfriend Aftab!
Yesterday only, we informed the college.
l never expected you guys
would come over!
This shows how much affection
you've towards her.
The worst part is...
she doesn't remember anything now...
Even me...she asked who l was!
She kind of lost her memories!!
lf you see her...
l think it will be good.
Sorry..l don't know why l am making
you guys stand here.
Just come in.
Please come inside
Malar...see who has come!
Please come inside.
They are your students.
Didn't l say... you were teaching in Kerala.
Hmm..Okay..
This is George.
Hi, George!
This is Shambu!
Koya and Aftab!
She's Malar's mother.
You guys talk..l'll be back now.
Mother...do l've to buy anything?
Jasmine flowers..
l'm sorry.
What did you say your name was?
-George -Ah!! George!
You were saying something?
Where are you going?
What happened?
l am going to Kodaikanal.
What for?
Arivazhagan had called.
They're getting married.
So, he's inviting us for
the pre-wedding reception....
You don't have to go to Kodiakanal.
l want to go.
How many times have you gone there?
l'll go and say..
What will you say?
That both of us were in love.
She doesn't even remember your name..
Then, what's the point of telling?
l don't know all that,
but l must go.
Even l've felt that
both of you were in love.
But forthe rest of the world,
you're only a student...
...and she's yourteacher.
l don't have the necessity
to prove everybody.
Then, how else are you
going to prove your love?
Apart from Malar,
who else knows about your affair?
Am l to prove infront of everybody .........!
lf you guys were in my position,
would you just booze and sit here?
George!! Why don't you think practically?
Ugh! Practical!
lt's very easy to advice !
Be in my shoes and see.
lt's not that we don't
understand your pain..
We don't mind coming too...
But what the hell are we supposed
to do after going there?
When you'd been there,
she didn't even remember your name.
Didn't you sit and weep like a kid?
That's enough.
''Malar (Flower),
in your absence all the colours''
''Which decorated me are fading off'
''lf you are not showing mercy
to come beside me''
''All the beautiful dreams are going away''
''The beats and rhythms which l have
kept deep inside my soul tenderly''
''Without anyone's knowledge
are coming out as tunes
and colours''
''You are raining inside
my broken heart''
''As a romantic rain this beautiful day''
''Malar (Flower),
my tiring body is waking up''
''Because of your lashing love.''
''O beauty, ''
''Malar (Flower), You are the rose flower
blossoming inside me''
2014 OCTOBER
-What about the doughnuts?
-Almost getting done.
Will you at least finish the
cleaning today?
Yes...right away.
After Doughnuts... switch over to Cakes.
Okay.
Hasn't Jojo come yet?
Not yet!! lt's just getting
time for majesty's arrival!
What happened to your proposal?
Oh!! l don't think it'll work out.
Don't rush.. lt'll happen
when the right time comes!
-Did you clean it?
- Yes.
Can't you guys put them in order?
Good morning sir
Good morning!
ls no one here to water these plants?
You are quite early for work!
Hi! Good morning!
Why are you late?
l'm asking , why you're late?
No..l got a bit late.
That's what l'm asking you, why?
l'd been to the church...
lt was my father's death anniversary!
ls that why you hang around
with plugged ears?
Did you shave today?
You look very handsome.
-Haven't you ever seen me shaved?
-No
l mean l have!
That's why l said you look handsome.
Can't you water those plants & otherthings?
l've already instructed them to do it.
Damn it!
What happened to that....
l've copied it on the C Drive.
C drive!! Hell!
Change your dress and come fast.
Pramod, Why the hell are you here for?.
l've just got a lil late today
and things go for a toss...
''lt's a new age''
''A brand new world''
''This world keeps changing
generation to generation''
''lt's a new age''
''A brand new world''
''This World keeps changing
generation to generation.''
''ln this world''
''While you are busy with your life''
''And while look back to your past''
''Please don't forget to laugh''
''ln this world''
''When you learn to forget''
''when you learn to forgive''
''Don't forget to laugh''
What's this? Hey....Sir...stop.
-ls there no valet parking here?
-What is that?
You hold this please.
Hold it please.
We've no parking for these kind of stuffs
lf my boss sees this,
he'll rip me apart!
Which is my horse?
Who's this on the horse?
Hold this..l'll be back now.
Please be back immediately!
There's no parking for this.
-What's your name?
- Baby!
He looks familiar.
-Don't you recognize him?
- No
Oh! One who's used to
roam around Gopu and our bridge.
Jeez! ls it Raining!
Aiswarya, go and get the order carefully.
Whole set up is really good!
-What's your name?
- Aiswarya!
Aiswarya, are you married?
No.
Do you live close by?
Yes! Short distance from here.
What's here to eat?
Tea..Coffee and cakes, sir.
So sweet..!
Sweet - Pastries and Cakes are there.
Oh! Then, get me a
marble cake and a medium tea
No medium tea..We've got regular tea
With or without masala...
and also different varieties of Pot tea.
POTTY
POT TEA, sir!
Aiswarya, someone is calling you there.
l'll get the order.
Not POTTY but POT TEA
Who are you?
l'm working here.
Tea maker, is it?
No, l'm the manager here.
-Manager?
- Yes
Your face looks very arrogant!
Give me the order, sir.
Get me a chicken samosa
We don't take KOZHl(Chicken) items here!
Though dressed up in a suit
l still can't get rid of the
nickname KOZHl(Womanizer)
Just mind your business!
You don't have to mock me, okay?
Okay. Give me the order.
Wait chap, l'll give you.
Who's this burglar behind?
That's our regular customer.
-Really?
- Yes
Then, get me a Bun and a cup of milk tea.
That's not Bun and milk tea.
lt's Veg Sandwich and Cold coffee!
l know. l wasjust testing you.
Get me that.
l wonder if he recognizes me!
-Couldn't you wash all these?
- OK
He's hardly changed!
Crazy guy!
Hello! Serve me on this table.
Eh?!
lt's already occupied!.
Serve it here. lt's ok!
-Hello!
- Hello!
-Fine?
-Sorry..What happened?
Who are you?
-Eh!!
- Who are you?
What's that??
Where do you live?
Bombay!
-Bombay? - Yeah!
Hello!! Serve me on my previous table only.
When l don't like lndians,
then, how Bombay people!!
Where is she?
Don't l've to serve it here?
Hello!
l need a cake....
Sorry. Shop is closed!
Hello! lt's for a surprise party!
No shops are open at this hour.
Actually, cleaning is on.
Oh! That doesn't matter!
Which cake do you need?
White forest
...1 kg!
-White forest!
- Please come.
Water...
Water..
No...not over there.
Should l write something?
Yeah! Happy Birthday, Appu!
No..Happy 25th Birthday Appu
okay
1Get the cover and packet ready
Quick!
Who's this Appu?
Appu is...my brother.
O God!! lt went wrong!
Shucks!! l could've written it rather.
Sorry!
Get another cake.
Don't make a mistake.
This is the last cake.
This time, it'll be perfect.
Won't it?
-ls that okay?
-Yeah, good!
Thank you.
-What's the cost?
- Rs.450
-Balance?
- Thank you.
Candles and knife are kept inside.
Convey my birthday wishes to your brother.
Convey my wishes too.
l'll surely convey!
-Okay - See you!
-Good night! - Good night!
Water..
Water!
Hey, you!
-Bye - Good night!
Nice girl, is'nt she?
Any idea of proposing her?
Oh no! That won't work out.
She may be from an affluent family
But l'm just a staff here.
Come on!!
Do you've any plans of proposing her, boss?
Hmmm......Go and finish cleaning!
l can understand.
When l called you boss this time,
you didn't say a word!
- Hello - Hello George!
lt's me, buddy!
ME? Who?
Don't you recognize me?
How will l be able to know
if you just tell me your ME?
Tell me your name.
Buddy, l'm Justin.
-Justy?
- Yes...College mate.
Yes Justy! Tell me.
Bro, my marriage is fixed.
l called to invite you
Oh! Your marriage is fixed?
Who's the bride?
Bride..don't you remember
Christy in my batch?
Christy?
Not Christy..but her relative!
Relative means..
That's..Her uncle's..
Okay..okay.
-How about Shambu and Koya?
- They are fine
-Send me their numbers in Whatsapp
- Yes, sure!
Hey...Shambu's that song....some Badam
Yes..lt's Pista song!
Ah! Pista song! lt was really superb!
Make him sing that song at my reception!
Sure! Anyhow, try calling him.
Do you remember our golden college days?
Of course!
How fantastic were your songs!!
Especially that Tamil song!
Where is our Malar miss now?
-Really miss our college days, isn't it?
Hmm!
Well, forget it! l've many people to invite.
-Do one thing! Send me their
numbers in Whatsapp. - Sure!
Coming Saturday is the Bachelor's party!
Must have a great blast!
-Hmm...okay.
- Bye, then
Where are you going? Hello..
Hello! Where do l get
a yellow Anarkali churidhar?
No idea!
What about a green one?
Green?
Hello!
Do you recognize me?
Oh! Hi!! You've been to
Cafv@ that day, is it?
The question mark episode!!
That was a funny ,Aoepisode' actually !
But Besides all that!!
We've an old connection between us.
What old connection?
Do you remember Mary chechi(sister)?
Mary George!
Yes! l've seen her around.
Ya, l sort of know her.
Come on!! l very well know
you were after Mary chechi(sister).
Let me go around and come.
By the time, l think it'll get over.
Haven't you seen me along
with Mary chechi(sister)?
Oh!hmmm...
We've even talked to each other.
ls it?
l'm Celine!
Oh!! Celine!
Mary chechi(sister)!
The guy we'd seen at church!
What's you name?
Mummy has told me not to
tell my name to strangers.
But l'll tell you. l'm Celine!
Celine!! Good!
Are you in the state syllabus or Cbse?
l don't know all that.
Will both of them get married?
Then, why didn't you tell me that day?
l thought you would recognize me..
And l was also running out of time.
Good!
Are you fine?
Yes! What do you do now?
l've completed my studies!
l'm doing designing now.
Okay...l see.
But this is Mens wear!
Do you buy your dresses from here?
-l'd been here to buy a
shirt for my cousin - Ok
l've picked up two shirts.
A small confusion!
Can you help me pick up one?
Yes!
Come
ls your brother..like..
tall and big..?
No...no.. He's pretty thin!
-Justy... - Yes.
Was yours, love or arranged marriage?
Don't you know? lt's Love marriage!
What did you say?
Means Love is Omnipresent!
Love is the main thing
present everywhere in this world!
What's your girl's name?
Her name is Evanya!
Unani?! lsn't that
a treatment?
lt's not Unani. lt's Evanya!
Evanya dear! You'll find it
pretty hard to call!
Talking about her....
l just remembered...!
l promised to give her a call today.
Let me go call her and come back
-Love talks huh? - Yes
What's your opinion about LOVE?
About LOVE?
l've a very good opinion about LOVE
Good opinion, is it?
PUPPY LOVE!
What PUPPY LOVE?!
You also loved and married
a Nair girl, right!
Didn't you feel it was
PUPPY LOVE then?
Just a minute! Why are you
talking about LOVE now?
Look at his mischievous smile!!
What's the matter?
Come on, tell us..
Do you guys remember Mary?
Mary? Which Mary?
12th grade Mary!
Ah ah! 12th grade Mary! So?
Now, she's married
and settled in US with 2 children.
Why her again, bro?
No illicit affairs!! Won't allow!
Do you guys remember
a child along with Mary those times?
-Who? - Do you remember Celine?
Hey, what's this?
-lt was a cockroach!!
-Cockroach? ln the Water?
Hello! Unani!
Unani?! Who's that?
Not Unani but Evanya, bro!
How many times have
l been telling you...
-Are you drunk, Justin?
-Ah!
Tell me the truth.
You promised me that you won't drink.
l didn't drink.
Now she's around 22 yrs old.
22 yrs?
Buddy! Difference of.Eight years!
So what?
Fahad and Nazriya...
they have a difference of 12 yrs!
But that's a bit too much!
That's not right.
lf that's not right,
then this is also not right.
-Too bad!
-lf that's bad, then this is also bad.
l don't mind..
Wait...to fall in love...
Where did you see her?
She'd been to the cafv@ one day.
The moment l saw her,
l got... some spark.
Let it be anything.
Coming to the cafv@...exchanging cakes...
Stop all those nonsense!..
Now you've a job!
Go to her house and propose.
No more old style, George!
Deal this with your parents.
-Parents dealings will be enough
- Yes
Do you mean l can go ahead and propose?
Go ahead hopefully.
Deal this with your parents.
Before dealing with parents,
Don't l've to tell this to her first?
what if l go and propose her first?
Go ahead confidently.
Don't take this vagabond along with you.
and when you go....You go YOURSELF
Until, now you've been
asking me not to go as myself
Now, why is this sudden change?
Earlier you were really a boring person!
But now, you've changed!
You are simply awesome now!
Where's the glass?
Like whom have they asked me to go...??
-What do you like to have?
- Banana roast?
You'll not get Banana roast here.
-Black tea?
- Just a minute.
One black tea and any cake.
Ok
What happened to the
proposal for which you went?
lt was as usual!
Hello!!
Give me a kiss and then let's talk!!
People are around.
I'm at Cafe Agape now.
Won't you come ....at 6 ,Ao0 clock?
The girl insists on B.Tech!
Where do l get this B.Tech now?
B. Tech! You'll get in Super market!
Don't provoke me!!
You've to use your brains to
complete such course.
Are you asking a 10th grade
dropout like me such questions?
Lower your voice, please.
Customers are reading.
Ok. Thank You!
Keep your voice down,
this ain't some market.
l told the fact.
-l'll take B.Tech but there's a problem.
-What problem?
Will l get a 12th grade certificate, then?
You haven't even passed 12th grade?!!
No, l mean..since my dad
fell from the coconut tree..
Am l looking alliance for such a person?
Get all this degree and then come to me.
Get your B.tech and then come to me.
Here is your black tea!
l don't want. You take it back.
Get a degree and then come to me.
Playing with me!
What nuisance is this!
This is not a fish market.
l'll text you later. Bye.
Hello!
Hey!! You were here?
l've been looking for you.
l was baking a Cake inside.
Oh!! Do you bake Cakes?
Hmm! l'm running this Cafv@, isn't it?
Are you alone?
Ah, that's..
How was the Cake you'd
taken the other day?
lt was good. Pretty good!
Wanna join..if not busy?
Yeah
Ah! You arrived at the right time!
Clean up this table.
Do you like to have anything else?
Get two pieces of Red velvet cake!
Which one... the one you baked, boss?
Don't call me Boss!!
Then, l also need one piece.
Give one piece to Baby also
Ah!!! So much build up!!
That tasty, huh?
Please wait.
-How is your dad doing?
- Fine!
Really yummy!
You like it?
Are you married?
Me? No! Why'd you ask?
Because your wife
can eat real delicious cakes.
Would you mind if l approach
your parents with a proposal?
Eh?
Would you mind if l approach with a
marriage proposal?
Hmm..Coming Sunday is my engagement.
You'll definitely get a
better girl than me.
Your cake is ready.
Was the cake delicious?
Do you have a pen?
Are you happily eating it all by yourself?.
-Boss baked it.-What?
Swallow it and then say,
l can hardly understand.
Boss baked it..Very delicious one!
Not much left....this is the last piece!
What's in it?
Nothing. Where is he?
He's behind there, near the lake
l think he's a little upset!
What happened?
Celine had come.
Both were chatting happily.
Later, l don't know what happened
He walked out angrily.
That girl had given a letter.
What...?
-What's that on the cover?
-Let me see!
What is inside the cover?.
Envelope inside the cover !!
-What has she written?
-l'll tell you later.
l'll tell you later.
You could have given it to him, is it?
Will anyone dare
put the head in a running heated oven?
That's what you've been
doing for these many years.
Don't disclose him about her letter.
l won't!
Hey, George!
Boss!
Boss! Don't commit suicide!
Come down.
Why did you climb up?
Please hold me
Oh!! He's too drunk!
Hold him.
What's this?
Absinthe!
Absinthe? What it is?!
..aAlcohol content!
Where's the glass?
Nice bottle!
Get the glass items! Quick.
l'll booze and fly as high as a kite!
Don't slip off and break it!
Bro, seems like her marriage is fixed.
Hey, get the glasses quickly.
Shambu, Sing a song.
-Song?-Ah!
''When l cast a net in the river''
''You pretty one, you appeared
with twinkling bangles''
''Be sure, you pick me
when you draw lots to marry''
No....not that song...
Some other song.
Then, l've a song
written and composed only by me.
You guys want to hear?.
Three of you listen here
''Don't want that girl,
Don't want this girl''
''Don't want any of them''
''Don't want love''
''We don't want love''
''Anyway here the total scene is contra''
Hey Hey...Spendid
Once more
''Don't want that girl,
Don't want this girl''
''Don't want any of them''
''Don't want love''
''We don't want love''
''Anyway here the total scene is contra''
''To walk closely, to sit near her,''
''To have 24/7 dating with her,''
''Though he followed her with difficulty''
''Tried different techniques,''
''No reply''
''Different costumes, drooling,''
''Don't want that girl,
Don't want love''
''Anyway here the total
scene is contra''
Can you get me a black coffee?
-Black coffee
-Need Dosa?-One Black coffee!
''Took loan and bought Audi car,''
''Borrowed bike from friends,''
''But no reply, Still no reply''
''Her parents drove him away''
''Her neighbours threw stones at him''
''His friends did not help him
and left him alone''
''That situation created
sentiments in her''
''She fell in love with him
and he became a hero''
''Everything changed out''
''Started taking out for dating''
''But after four months broke up''
Hello Cafv@!
Hello, it's me Celine
Hmm!
Today is my engagement.
So?
l'm totally confused!
What should l say, Yes or No?
Pray to God and take a strong decision.
Who's that?
Who's this?
l'm Jojo!
Put the phone down, fool.
No point advising kids these days!!
Why do you tell me all this?
That's...l...Sorry..
l don't have to talk to
someone else's girl!
''He wasn't aware of the board
,AoBeware of dog'''
''He didn't think it'll
create a scene''
''He jumped the wall of her house''
''But that ended up in plastering his legs''
''Even after her brothers beat him up,''
''Even after his both legs were plastered,''
''Even after she ditched him,''
''Even after his friends scorned him,''
''Made him drink the whole night,''
''He is still not worth even a penny''
''How many times should l tell you,''
''Don't you understand Malayalam''
''Don't want that girl''
''Don't want this girl''
''Don't want any of them''
''Don't want love''
''We don't want love''
''Anyway here the tota
l scene is contra (contrary)!''
''Don't want that girl''
''Don't want this girl''
''Don't want any of them''
''Don't want love''
''We don't want love''
''Anyway here the tota
l scene is contra (contrary)!''
Come on go...horse..go
Let's go
Who's this, buddy?
That's Celine, who was along with Mary.
This is Celine?
This is what l've been trying to
make you understand past few days.
-Yes, this is Celine!
-Oh so this is Celine!
Hold it up right.
lt's been two days since l left home!
''O Moon, do you have a small casket
of mandhara flowers, rubies''
''Gold, honey and herbal roots ?''
''Are there skylark's songs ?''
''When waves of ecstasy rise
in the heart, silence sings''
''ln the platter of vegetables,
one potato grandma said, ''
''Little one, have food in the
leaf bowl and swing''.
Hey, it's not like that.
See!! This is what happened to me also.
Pramod! Get me a Scissor! Here!
ls the height correct?
Baby Cheta(brother), you placed
infant Jesus so early?
What's wrong?
-What Christian are you! ,AiRC!
Only at 12 ,Ao0 clock we're
supposed to keep!
l won't be available at 12 ,Ao0 clock.
l'll go to sleep.
Mummy has made grape wine!
Really? Ok.
We'll have a great blast
having wine and bursting crackers!
Okay!
Give this to mom.
Happy Christmas!
Come early, otherwise l'll
finish off everything!
l need a Christmas cake.
Which one?
Red Velvet!
ls one kg enough?
Yes!
Rectangle!
No Rectangle...Only round is available.
Doesn't matter. Will be fine!
Any dedication?
No!
How is your husband?
Which husband?
You told about your marriage, then?
Didn't l ring you up on the
day of my engagement?
Later, l was totally confused.
Unable to make any decision,
l was totally mind boggled.
Then?
At last, l said YES
Oh!!
And thereafter, during the reception....
lt was a big scene.
What happened?
Where did you do your makeup?
Treesa Aunty!
Have you been to Bombay?
Yeah!
There..at the Red street.....,
You look like a whore from there!
And it's so horrible looking at you
in front of my family and my friends.
And how do you think l can tolerate you?
Hi Celine!
Hi Rony! l'm Celine's friend
l'm Nelson.
-Rony brother!! One photo please.
-Take it.
-Please, look here.
-Not possible
Will you smile please?
Please give a pose, Rony bro.
l said l can't!
Thus, Pappa called off the marriage.
You know, there's some stuff he inhales
through his nose at most times.....
Snuff-Tobacco?
Not that!
A stuff inhaled through nose
like the one seen in English movies..
Oh! Charlie!
Eh!!
Cocaine!
Yes, that!
lt seems lf you inhale that,
you can't see anything around,
and needlessly talk rubbish!
He still calls me.
Can't you avoid him, then?
No point in that.
He'll call and blow his own trumpet!
lf l don't attend, there will be
around 40 missed calls.
Papa said we can lodge a
police complaint.
But, what can Police do about it?
He really deserves to be bashed up good!
Here....Look at this! He's calling!
Can l attend?
Sure!
-Hello
- Hello!
Give the phone to Celine!
My name is George
George? Who are you?
l'm Celine's..
Your marriage's been called off, right?
Then, why do you still
call and disturb her?
Who the hell are you to ask this?
Are you her dad?
Give her the phone, you creep!
l say, give the phone.
''Eyes are getting red''
''Teeth are biting in anger''
''The whole body is sweating''
''Veins and arteries are pumping up''
''Muscles are stretching out''
''Heart is breathing fast''
in a rhythmic fashion''
''Hands and legs are shivering''
''And craving for a fight
The whole body is getting aggressive''
''And shivering from top to toe''
Few people have come.
l'll call you later. Bye!
Who are you all?
What do you want?
GEORGE WEDS CELlNE
Let me tell all of you one thing.
This is all fine, but while serving,
serve the guests delightfully,
Or else, things will go haywire,
mind you!
''lt's a new age,
A brand new world''
''This world keeps changing
generation to generation''
''lt's a new age,
A brand new world''
''This world keeps changing
generation to generation''
l've a doubt for a long time.
Why are you guys hitting me?
Will you hike the petrol price, huh?
''Dark Girl, without seeing you one day''
''l felt sad and turned into a beetle.''
''ln my rejoicing heart,
l'm thinking of you sitting alone.''
''ln my rejoicing heart, ''
lf l put Bob Marley T-shirt,
you will arrest me...is'nt it?
''Dark Girl, without seeing you one day''
''l felt sad and turned into a beetle.''
Roads are full of Potholes and traffic!
-Keep your head straight
-Please don't hit me anymore.
l doubt if there's some misunderstanding.
Your name?
-l'm Roney!
- Roney!
Roney Vargese!
Vargese ah? Shucks!! Mistake!
l'm sorry!
Sorry! We've mistaken.
Ah, Yes, l too felt the same!
Sorry, lt was a mistake!
Otherwise, how do l connect
with Petrol, Road ..Bob Marley..
..all were very irrelevant to me.
Happy Christmas!
See you! Sorry, please don't mistake!
-Mistakingly... -Bro,
we're all friends, right?
Sorry bro!
-Happy Christmas!-Happy Christmas
Boss! Was it really a
mistake from our side?
Hello! Why don't you untie me and go?
Malar, is it?
-Who invited her?.
- Me only!
Who told you?
Celine!
Does George know about this?
No.
You could've told him?
What for? He is happy now.
l was pretty sure that
he will marry her only.
But you weren't saying this
forthese many years.
Do you remember the letter
she sent through Jojo?
-Written on a tissue paper
-Yes
Buddy! l read it!
-lt's completely wrong just like his writing
-Yes!
Oh, l see!
Then, this is a perfect match!
Correct partner!
l wonder how would their children be!!
Nothing!
What a naughty smile!!
God unified the flowers
which cannot move with butterflies!
For you flowers which can move,.....
.....He bestowed to all of you,
butterflies as the emotion of LOVE !
''The Butterfly is mentally mental,
so is love''
Mummy has told me not to tell
my name to the strangers
But l will say.
My name is Celine.
Celine! Good!
Are you in state syllabus or CBSE?
l don't know.
Will they both get married?
God only knows!
Only God knows who will be marrying me!
Shall l marry you?
Won't you find a better girl than me?
Really?
-Do you like the ice-cream?
- Hmm, yes!
Have it.
Her beehive like hair!! Ugh!
Get lost, you Chala(Sardine)Mary!
www.moviesubtitles.org